{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 11 + 12?",
      "options": [
        30,
        23,
        26,
        28
      ],
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 13 + 80?",
      "options": [
        86,
        93,
        92,
        99
      ],
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 77 + 20?",
      "options": [
        97,
        89,
        95,
        88
      ],
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 19 + 66?",
      "options": [
        83,
        81,
        95,
        85
      ],
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 47 + 48?",
      "options": [
        87,
        95,
        92,
        97
      ],
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 27 + 42?",
      "options": [
        68,
        69,
        64,
        71
      ],
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 82 + 10?",
      "options": [
        85,
        92,
        93,
        91
      ],
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 34 + 46?",
      "options": [
        80,
        88,
        85,
        75
      ],
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 47 + 18?",
      "options": [
        73,
        65,
        74,
        60
      ],
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 55 + 22?",
      "options": [
        77,
        84,
        80,
        71
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 26 + 13?",
      "options": [
        29,
        35,
        41,
        39
      ],
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 64 + 25?",
      "options": [
        89,
        98,
        79,
        88
      ],
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 16 + 23?",
      "options": [
        31,
        39,
        40,
        45
      ],
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 47 + 34?",
      "options": [
        73,
        81,
        72,
        88
      ],
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 39 + 51?",
      "options": [
        98,
        90,
        84,
        91
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 16 + 12?",
      "options": [
        30,
        35,
        28,
        31
      ],
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 36 + 22?",
      "options": [
        58,
        64,
        62,
        48
      ],
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 21 + 40?",
      "options": [
        66,
        53,
        62,
        61
      ],
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 26 + 20?",
      "options": [
        46,
        53,
        39,
        48
      ],
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 17 + 60?",
      "options": [
        77,
        79,
        87,
        78
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 11 + 74?",
      "options": [
        80,
        89,
        86,
        85
      ],
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 20 + 74?",
      "options": [
        94,
        95,
        87,
        93
      ],
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 17 + 46?",
      "options": [
        67,
        63,
        66,
        61
      ],
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 30 + 62?",
      "options": [
        92,
        98,
        93,
        89
      ],
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 37 + 59?",
      "options": [
        96,
        91,
        86,
        95
      ],
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 32 + 48?",
      "options": [
        75,
        80,
        89,
        84
      ],
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 64 + 18?",
      "options": [
        80,
        83,
        89,
        82
      ],
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 52 + 29?",
      "options": [
        74,
        77,
        83,
        81
      ],
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 61 + 29?",
      "options": [
        96,
        87,
        95,
        90
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 44 + 53?",
      "options": [
        97,
        94,
        91,
        90
      ],
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 75 + 20?",
      "options": [
        89,
        86,
        95,
        97
      ],
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 36 + 21?",
      "options": [
        48,
        57,
        55,
        61
      ],
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 25 + 26?",
      "options": [
        54,
        53,
        60,
        51
      ],
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 12 + 11?",
      "options": [
        20,
        22,
        13,
        23
      ],
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 24 + 46?",
      "options": [
        72,
        78,
        70,
        75
      ],
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 23 + 37?",
      "options": [
        61,
        60,
        54,
        69
      ],
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 12 + 82?",
      "options": [
        93,
        94,
        90,
        88
      ],
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 19 + 50?",
      "options": [
        64,
        67,
        62,
        69
      ],
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 29 + 19?",
      "options": [
        48,
        39,
        55,
        56
      ],
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 27 + 50?",
      "options": [
        87,
        75,
        77,
        73
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 19 + 79?",
      "options": [
        94,
        98,
        91,
        88
      ],
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 53 + 28?",
      "options": [
        81,
        89,
        72,
        83
      ],
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 52 + 32?",
      "options": [
        77,
        85,
        84,
        91
      ],
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 31 + 46?",
      "options": [
        77,
        80,
        87,
        83
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 30 + 16?",
      "options": [
        38,
        46,
        44,
        36
      ],
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 42 + 18?",
      "options": [
        60,
        63,
        61,
        51
      ],
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 17 + 20?",
      "options": [
        46,
        37,
        33,
        27
      ],
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 42 + 13?",
      "options": [
        65,
        57,
        61,
        55
      ],
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 70 + 21?",
      "options": [
        84,
        91,
        88,
        83
      ],
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Level 6: What is 10 + 57?",
      "options": [
        67,
        76,
        73,
        72
      ],
      "answer": 67
    }
  ]
}